<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="https://www.kargihome/rss.css" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>kargihome &amp; Company</title><description>Address: 39 Bury New Road, Prestwich, Manchester, M25 9JY    Telephone: 0161 798 8000</description><link>https://www.kargihome</link><language>en-gb</language><webMaster>viewings@kargihome</webMaster><generator>www.AcquaintCRM.co.uk</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://www.acquaintcrm.co.uk/customers/AUBR/logo.gif</url><title>kargihome &amp; Company</title><link>https://www.kargihome</link></image><item><title>5 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Prestwich £850,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Prestwich-Park-Road-South-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR5366.htm</link><description>kargihome Estate Agents are delighted to offer for sale this five bedroomed, 3 bathroomed, period semi detached property offering an abundance of character throughout along with unbelievably spacious family accommodation over three floors plus a large basement.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 11:50:44 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Prestwich-Park-Road-South-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR5366.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Bungalow, Whitefield £280,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Wingate-Drive-Whitefield-Manchester-pi-AUBR6490.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to offer to the market this detached two bedroom bungalow located on a quiet cul-de-sac offering easy access to local shops and transport links. The property is in need of updating but offers a great opportunity to create your perfect home. Internal viewing is vital.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 05:26:56 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Wingate-Drive-Whitefield-Manchester-pi-AUBR6490.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Flat, Salford £150,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Milton-Court-Salford-pi-AUBR6614.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to bring to the market this 1st floor apartment situated in a popular development offering easy access for local shops, transport links and places of worship. The apartment is presented to a high standard having been recently renovated.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 04:44:50 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Milton-Court-Salford-pi-AUBR6614.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Manchester £295,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Bland-Road-Manchester-pi-AUBR6746.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this 3 bedroom semi detached house located in a popular residential area offering easy access to local shops, transport links, schools and places of worship. The property offers great potential for extension subject to the usual permissions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 03:26:39 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Bland-Road-Manchester-pi-AUBR6746.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Manchester £330,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Salisbury-Drive-Manchester-pi-AUBR6828.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to bring to the market this three bedroom semi detached house located on a sought after road in Sedgley Park, the property benefits from two separate reception rooms and off street parking for two vehicles. Local shops, schools and places of worship are in close by.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 04:45:57 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Salisbury-Drive-Manchester-pi-AUBR6828.htm</guid></item><item><title>1 Bedroom Studio, Salford £750.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Sandy-Grove-Salford-pi-AUBR6934.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are pleased to present this second floor studio flat, in a superb location.  The studio has a kitchen/lounge area,  bathroom with a bath and overhead shower.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 04:32:54 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Sandy-Grove-Salford-pi-AUBR6934.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Prestwich £280,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Brooklands-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR6990.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this semi detached house located on a popular residential location offering easy access to local shops, schools, places of worship and transport links. The property would make a great family home and is offered with no chain.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 12:38:07 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Brooklands-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR6990.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Terrace, Prestwich £199,950.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Polefield-Grove-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7038.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to offer to the market this Mid Terraced, Three bedroom house having two reception rooms, The property is available vacant or with a sitting tenant. Local shops, schools, transport links are all within close proximity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 09:34:52 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Polefield-Grove-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7038.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Apartment, Salford £235,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Upper-Park-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7076.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this 3rd Floor (lift assisted) apartment offering 3 bedrooms and in need of modernisation throughout. The property is within close proximity to local transport links, shops and places and worship.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 01:29:24 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Upper-Park-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7076.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Salford £500,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Leicester-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7106.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to offer this substantial, four bedroomed, semi detached property occupying a great position along sought after Leicester Road. Needing modernisation but offering great potential.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 01:05:42 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Leicester-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7106.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom Detached, Salford £600,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Cavendish-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7140.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are pleased to offer to the market this nicely proportioned four bedroom (1 EnSuite) Detached family home located on a quiet enclave off Cavendish Road, located offering convenient access to local shops, schools and places of worship. A great opportunity to create a true family home.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 02:04:09 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Cavendish-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7140.htm</guid></item><item><title>6 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Salford £499,950.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Devonshire-Street-Salford-pi-AUBR7154.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this three Storey end town house comprising of six bedrooms and two reception rooms, situated in a popular residential area offering convenient access for local shops, transport links and places of worship.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 11:23:59 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Devonshire-Street-Salford-pi-AUBR7154.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Prestwich £250,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Albert-Avenue-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7158.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this three bedroom semi detached house offering great potential for extension (subject to the usual permissions)  located within close proximity to local shops, schools, places of worship and transport links. Ideal investment or first time buy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 10:40:31 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Albert-Avenue-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7158.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Terrace, Darwen £575.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Sydney-Street-Darwen-pi-AUBR5051.htm</link><description>kargihome homes are pleased to present this good sized two bedroom mid terraced home located on the edge of the Darwen with excellent access to local town amenities and moments from the travel network. Viewings highly recommended.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 01:18:44 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Sydney-Street-Darwen-pi-AUBR5051.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Prestwich £310,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Windsor-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7217.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this Semi Detached three bedroom family house situated in a popular residential location offering easy access to lock shops, schools, transport links and places of worship. The property also benefits from two reception rooms and good size garden.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 11:07:42 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Windsor-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7217.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom Detached, Salford £625,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Tetlow-Lane-Salford-pi-AUBR7220.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this detached family home, located in a prime residential location. The property benefits from four bedrooms (1 En Suite) along with three reception rooms. Local shops, schools and places of worship are all within easy access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 12:24:43 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Tetlow-Lane-Salford-pi-AUBR7220.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Prestwich £325,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Dovedale-Avenue-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7245.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to bring to the market this extended family home consisting of three good bedrooms and an extended diner kitchen, the property offers convenient access to local shops, schools, transport links and places of worship. A great family home with viewing highly recommended.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 01:41:04 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Dovedale-Avenue-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7245.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Detached, Salford £500,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Moor-End-Avenue-Salford-pi-AUBR7264.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this extended, detached dormer bungalow, located on a quiet cul-de-sac off Bury New Road. The property comprises of three bedrooms and two reception rooms and offers convenient access to local shops, schools, transport links and places of worship.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 05:30:28 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Moor-End-Avenue-Salford-pi-AUBR7264.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom Detached, Prestwich £590,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Castle-Hill-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR428.htm</link><description>kargihome Estate Agents are pleased to offer this impressive and pleasantly situated detached family home with the benefit of four  bedrooms, a garage plus driveway, gas central heating and double glazing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 10:51:15 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Castle-Hill-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR428.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Apartment, Salford £425,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Wellington-Street-East-Salford-pi-AUBR7306.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to bring to the market this 1st floor apartment consisting of three bedrooms (1 en suite). The property benefits from a Kosher kitchen which also has a Succah roof. Ideally located for local amenities, transport links and places of worship.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:58:25 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Wellington-Street-East-Salford-pi-AUBR7306.htm</guid></item><item><title>6 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Salford £775,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-New-Hall-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7319.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to bring to the market this stunning new build semi detached house which is set over 3 floors and boasts six bedrooms (1 en suite), the property also benefits from a kosher kitchen, succah roof and off street parking. Situated offering easy access to local amenities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 02:00:54 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-New-Hall-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7319.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Salford £375,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Norwood-Avenue-Salford-pi-AUBR7326.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to bring to the market this semi detached, three bedroom house situated in a popular location offering convenient access to local shops, schools, places of worship and transport links. The property makes an ideal family home and benefits from a sizable basement also.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 11:09:56 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Norwood-Avenue-Salford-pi-AUBR7326.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Salford £625,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Vernon-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7305.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to offer to the market this substantial semi detached house which benefits from four bedrooms, two reception rooms and a diner kitchen. The property also boasts a nicely proportioned front and rear garden. The property is nicely presented throughout and in a great location.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 10:27:54 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Vernon-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7305.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Bungalow, Salford £360,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Moor-End-Avenue-Salford-pi-AUBR7322.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this detached bungalow located on a quiet cul-de-sac off Bury New Road, the property benefits from 2/3 bedrooms (depending on use of one of the rooms). Local shops, schools and places of worship are all easily accessible. Requires modernisation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 11:49:57 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Moor-End-Avenue-Salford-pi-AUBR7322.htm</guid></item><item><title>1 Bedroom Flat, Prestwich £99,950.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Bury-New-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7133.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are pleased to bring to the market this second floor, one bedroom apartment located conveniently to Prestwich Village and benefiting from a residents only carpark. The property requires full renovation and is available to cash buyers only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 11:39:09 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Bury-New-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7133.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Bury £299,995.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Manchester-Road-Bury-pi-AUBR7341.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this three bedroom semi detached house located in a popular residential location offering convenient access to local shops, schools and transport links. The property is presented to a good standard and makes a great family home.</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:48:25 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Manchester-Road-Bury-pi-AUBR7341.htm</guid></item><item><title>0 Bedroom Garage, Manchester £80.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Nuttall-Avenue-Manchester-pi-AUBR7210.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are offering this detached garage situated at the head of a quiet cul-de-sac, the motorway network is within close proximity as is Bury Old Road one of the main routes between Manchester and Bury.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 05:14:09 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Nuttall-Avenue-Manchester-pi-AUBR7210.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Salford £280,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Mesnefield-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7360.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this semi detached, three bedroom house occupying a corner plot offering potential for extension (subject to the usual permissions) the property is nicely kept throughout, shops, schools and transport links are easily accessible. Ideal first time buy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 10:56:12 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Mesnefield-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7360.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Bungalow, Royton £235,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Bodmin-Close-Royton-Oldham-pi-AUBR7374.htm</link><description>We are delighted  to offer this well presented  three bedroom semi detached dormer bungalow on a larger plot with larger gardens, perfect for the growing family or downsizers alike. There are beautiful walks close by along with Royton centre.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 01:11:07 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Bodmin-Close-Royton-Oldham-pi-AUBR7374.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom Detached, Salford £700,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Legh-Street-Salford-pi-AUBR6754.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Company are pleased to offer to the market this extended detached family home which boasts four bedrooms (1 en suite), four reception areas including a Succah and Pesach kitchen, situated in a sought after location close to many local amenities, places of worship &amp; Schools.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 03:34:17 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Legh-Street-Salford-pi-AUBR6754.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Prestwich £325,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Parksway-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR6480.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to offer to the market this extended semi detached, three bedroom house. Located in a poplar location having convenient access to local shops, schools, transport links and places of worship.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 02:04:37 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Parksway-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR6480.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Prestwich £285,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Salisbury-Drive-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7378.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this elevated semi detached house offering three bedrooms and two connecting reception rooms, located within easy access of local shops, schools and places of worship. A great starter family home which is offered with no onward chain.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 04:32:12 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Salisbury-Drive-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7378.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Terrace, Oldham £170,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Kelverlow-Oldham-pi-AUBR7312.htm</link><description>We are pleased to bring to the market this  three bedroom terraced house in the heart of Oldham completely beautifully renovated to a high standard. The property would make a nice ready to go home.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:52:08 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Kelverlow-Oldham-pi-AUBR7312.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Salford £600,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Leicester-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR6756.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are pleased to bring to the market this substantial Four bedroom Semi Detached, family home situated in a sought after location in Broughton Park. Local shops, places of worship, schools and bus routes are all within easy access. The property requires general modernisation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 05:28:48 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Leicester-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR6756.htm</guid></item><item><title>5 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Salford £525,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Norwood-Avenue-Salford-pi-AUBR7206.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to bring to the market this beautifully extended and presented semi detached house which is set over three floors and offers five bedrooms (1 En Suite) along with two reception rooms and stunning diner kitchen. Popular location and offered with no onward chain.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 10:11:24 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Norwood-Avenue-Salford-pi-AUBR7206.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Salford £595,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Castleton-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR4362.htm</link><description>kargihome Estate Agents are pleased to offer this extremely delightful, extended, four bedroomed (main with en suite) semi detached family home with spacious, modern living accommodation throughout and enviably situated in this discreet cul de sac just off Stanley Road.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 10:38:59 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Castleton-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR4362.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom Detached, Prestwich £775,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Danesway-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7389.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to offer this nicely presented and extended detached family home to the market, the property benefits from 4/5 bedrooms (1 En Suite) three reception rooms and is situated in a sought after location offering convenient access to local shops, schools and places of worship</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 11:15:03 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Danesway-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7389.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom End Terrace, Salford £395,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Leicester-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR5482.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this end terraced house which is set of three floors and has four bedrooms along with two reception rooms, located in a sought after location offering convenient access to local shops, schools, transport links and place of worship.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 09:08:27 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Leicester-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR5482.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Apartment, London £399,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Regents-Park-Road-London-pi-AUBR7435.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to offer for sale this 3 bed, 2nd floor apartment, providing the opportunity to refurbish it according to your dreams. Currently with exposed floorboards, so the refurbishment can commence immediately, Ample space, with lots of sunlight flooding into all rooms.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 12:56:53 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Regents-Park-Road-London-pi-AUBR7435.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Flat, Prestwich £150,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-St-Anns-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7349.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this 2nd floor, two bedroom apartment located in a quiet development which is a short distance from Prestwich Village which offers a multitude of shops, bars and restaurants. Local transport links are also easily accessible. There is no onward chain</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:12:46 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-St-Anns-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7349.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Maisonette, Salford £275,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Kingston-Close-Salford-pi-AUBR5908.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co offer to the market this nicely proportioned 1st floor maisonette which benefits from two double bedrooms along with two reception rooms, the property is in need of general modernisation throughout. Located at the head of a quiet cul de sac with easy access to places of worship</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 01:40:36 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Kingston-Close-Salford-pi-AUBR5908.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Prestwich £325,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Bishops-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR5905.htm</link><description>kargihome Estate Agents are pleased to bring to the market this three bedroom semi detached house having two connecting reception rooms, the property has previoulsy had plans passed for a wrap around extension, located within close proximity to local shops, schools and places of worship.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 04:33:51 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Bishops-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR5905.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Prestwich £375,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Sunnyfield-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7441.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to bring to the market this extended four bedroom semi detached house one of which has an en suite, the property benefits from a beautifully kept and large back garden and well presented throughout. Local shops, schools and transport links are within easy reach.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 10:49:38 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Sunnyfield-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7441.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom Detached, Whitefield £495,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Standmoor-Road-Whitefield-Manchester-pi-AUBR7426.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to bring to the market this nicely proportioned and extended detached family home, the property offers four good bedrooms, two reception rooms along with a lovely diner kitchen, the property has beautifully landscaped gardens to the front and rear.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 01:03:02 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Standmoor-Road-Whitefield-Manchester-pi-AUBR7426.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Prestwich £325,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Rochester-Avenue-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7438.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to bring to the market this nicely proportioned three bedroom semi detached house having two connecting reception rooms, the property offers convenient access to local shops, schools and places of worship and also has the benefit of off street parking.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 02:17:48 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Rochester-Avenue-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7438.htm</guid></item><item><title>5 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Salford £695,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Vernon-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR4301.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to bring to the market this extended family home which offers accommodation over three floors and boasts five bedrooms (1 En Suite) along with three reception rooms and a Succah. Conveniently located for shops, schools, places of worship and transport links.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 02:45:15 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Vernon-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR4301.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Prestwich £290,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Albert-Avenue-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7473.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to offer this semi detached family home which benefits from three bedrooms and two connected reception rooms. Located in a sought after location within close proximity to local shops, schools, places of worship and transport links, driveway and well proportioned garden.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 11:09:43 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Albert-Avenue-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7473.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Terrace, Prestwich £210,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Woodward-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7464.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this mid quasi semi detached house which comprises of three bedrooms, the property requires cosmetic modernisation throughout. The property offers convenient access for local shops, schools and bus routes and is an ideal first time buy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 01:55:52 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Woodward-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7464.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Salford £270,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Littleton-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR6714.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to bring to the market this beautifully presented and proportioned four bedroom (1 en suite) semi detached house, the property makes a great family home having nicely proportioned rooms throughout along with a great sized garden.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 10:13:21 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Littleton-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR6714.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Prestwich £300,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Ladythorn-Court-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7431.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this semi detached house which offers three bedrooms, two connecting reception rooms and conservatory. The property is in need of general updating throughout and benefits from a quiet location, there is a garage to the rear. Available with no chain.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 05:24:08 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Ladythorn-Court-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7431.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Prestwich £475,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Butt-Hill-Avenue-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7104.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this four bedroom semi detached family home, located on a quiet cul-de-sac offering convenient access to local shops, schools and transport links. The property is in need of general modernisation throughout.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:42:03 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Butt-Hill-Avenue-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7104.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Terrace, Prestwich £975.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Bailey-Street-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7303.htm</link><description>kargihome Estate Agents are pleased to offer this modern and beautifully designed, 2 bedroom terraced property with a rear yard &amp; off-street parking.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 04:48:21 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Bailey-Street-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7303.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Salford £260,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Oaklands-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7512.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this semi detached family home which offers three bedrooms and two reception rooms along with lovely landscaped gardens and basement which offers scope for full conversion. Offering easy access to local shops, transport links and schools.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 05:20:35 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Oaklands-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7512.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Terrace, Prestwich £315,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Dashwood-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7521.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are pleased to bring to the market this mid terraced house which offers three bedrooms (1 En Suite) and is set over three floors. The property is ideally located for walking to Prestwich Village with the local bars &amp; restaurants it has to offer along with shops and transport links.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:31:12 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Dashwood-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7521.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Terrace, Salford £350,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Wellington-Street-East-Salford-pi-AUBR7242.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are offering to the market this mid terraced three bedroom house having two connecting reception rooms and single storey extension to the rear, the property is in need of modernisation throughout but offers convenient access to local shops, schools and places of worship.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 04:10:15 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Wellington-Street-East-Salford-pi-AUBR7242.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Manchester £295,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Haversham-Road-Manchester-pi-AUBR7010.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this semi detached, three bedroom house located in a popular location offering convenient access to local shops, schools, places of worship and transport links. The property is offered with no onward chain.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 11:59:49 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Haversham-Road-Manchester-pi-AUBR7010.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Prestwich £325,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Chatsworth-Avenue-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7534.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this three bedroom semi detached house situated off Heywood Road, offering easy access to local shops and being a short distance from Prestwich Village. The property offers scope for a side extension (subject to permissions)</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 03:16:55 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Chatsworth-Avenue-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7534.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Salford £320,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Bury-Old-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7552.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this elevated three bedroom semi detached house offering convenient access to local shops, schools, places of worship and transport links. The property is ideal for young families and first time buyers alike and with no onward chain.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 03:55:56 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Bury-Old-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7552.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Flat, Prestwich £210,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Eagles-Nest-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7551.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this ground floor two bedroom apartment which opens at the rear to the communal garden. Sought after development offered nicely proportioned rooms and a shared double garage. Local shops and transport links are a short distance away.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 04:18:10 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Eagles-Nest-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7551.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Detached, Prestwich £300,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-St-Margarets-Close-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7515.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are pleased to bring to the market this Detached, three bedroom home located within close proximity to Heaton Park along with offering easy access to local shops, schools and transport links, the property is offered with no onward chain and would make an ideal first time buy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 12:19:17 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-St-Margarets-Close-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7515.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Flat, Prestwich £285,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Sedgley-Park-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR6672.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are pleased to bring to the market this ground floor, two bedroom apartment having an en suite to the main bedroom in a gated development, the property is nicely proportioned and offers lovely high ceilings. Offers easy access to local shops, transport and places of worship.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 03:38:24 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Sedgley-Park-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR6672.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom Terrace, Salford £350,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Murray-Street-Salford-pi-AUBR7554.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this mid terraced house set over three floors, the property benefits from two reception rooms along with four bedrooms, the property is in need of cosmetic modernisation throughout. Sought after location offering easy access to local shops, schools</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:38:20 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Murray-Street-Salford-pi-AUBR7554.htm</guid></item><item><title>0 Bedroom Retail / Commercial, Lees £1,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-High-Street-Lees-Oldham-pi-AUBR7562.htm</link><description>We are pleased to market a ground floor self contained shop unit suitable for a variety of uses.  Located in a popular established location within the centre of Lees village on High Street.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 12:21:50 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-High-Street-Lees-Oldham-pi-AUBR7562.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Apartment, Salford £2,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Waterpark-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR5902.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are pleased to offer this luxury, two bedroomed, ground floor apartment with extremely spacious living accommodation and situated in this modern, exclusive and superior development located along Waterpark Road close to its junction with Upper Park Road.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 04:14:34 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Waterpark-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR5902.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Terrace, Radcliffe £900.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Cross-Lane-Radcliffe-Manchester-pi-AUBR6919.htm</link><description>kargihome Homes Ltd are pleased to offer for rent this well presented 2 bedroom mid terrace property comprising of : Grey carpets and white walls throughout, lounge, dining room, modern fitted kitchen, good size rear yard.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 11:16:43 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Cross-Lane-Radcliffe-Manchester-pi-AUBR6919.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Flat, Broughton Park £795.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Stanley-Road-Broughton-Park-Salford-pi-AUBR4780.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are pleased to offer to rent this ground floor, 2 bed apartment, situated in Lincoln Court on Stanley Road, Broughton Park.&lt;br /&gt;The apartment is available immediately and briefly comprises; hallway, 2 double bedrooms, Jack &amp; Jill bathroom, large lounge/diner and kitchen.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 11:35:16 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Stanley-Road-Broughton-Park-Salford-pi-AUBR4780.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Radcliffe £189,950.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Rossall-Avenue-Radcliffe-Manchester-pi-AUBR7555.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to bring to the market this two bedroom mid quasi semi, conveniently located for local shops, schools and transport links, Radcliffe centre is a short distance away also. The property makes an ideal investment or first time buy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 03:32:49 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Rossall-Avenue-Radcliffe-Manchester-pi-AUBR7555.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Flat, New Hall Road £1,050.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Devonshire-Court-New-Hall-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR4641.htm</link><description>kargihome Estate Agents are pleased to offer this spacious freshly painted, two bedroomed, third floor, lift-assisted apartment. Offering good sized accommodation throughout and with the benefit of upvc double glazing, gas central heating &amp; brand new Kosher kitchen.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 04:47:30 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Devonshire-Court-New-Hall-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR4641.htm</guid></item><item><title>1 Bedroom Apartment, Broughton Green £800.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Green-View-Broughton-Green-Salford-pi-AUBR2099.htm</link><description>kargihome Estate Agents are pleased to offer this modern, one bedroomed, first floor apartment located in the popular Broughton Green development and offering electric storage heating, double glazing and security intercom. Offered unfurnished but with kitchen appliances.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 11:29:44 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Green-View-Broughton-Green-Salford-pi-AUBR2099.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Detached Bungalow, Salford £1,650.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Bury-Old-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7577.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are pleased to bring to the market this detached bungalow, comprising of two bedrooms and two reception rooms along with a conservatory. The property is located in a sought after area, offering convenient access to transport links, local shops and places of worship.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 03:46:53 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Bury-Old-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7577.htm</guid></item><item><title>1 Bedroom Apartment, Manchester £950.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Great-Marlborough-Street-Manchester-pi-AUBR5643.htm</link><description>kargihome Estate Agents are pleased to offer this stunning, ground floor, one bedroomed, one bathroom,  secure gated apartment located at the edge of the city centre close to Oxford Road. The accommodation comprises: Entrance hall with storage, lounge and open plan kitchen and good sized bathroom.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 05:11:53 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Great-Marlborough-Street-Manchester-pi-AUBR5643.htm</guid></item><item><title>5 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Salford £650,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Leicester-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR5563.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to bring to the market this extended, substantial semi detached house which offers five bedrooms (1 en suite) along with two reception rooms and Succah along with Pesach kitchen. Sought after location close to shops, schools and places of worship.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 09:27:36 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Leicester-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR5563.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Prestwich £275,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Overbrook-Drive-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR6436.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are pleased to bring to the market this three bedroom semi detached family home located in a popular residential location offering convenient access for local shops, transport links, schools and places of worship. The property requires cosmetic updating throughout.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 03:41:22 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Overbrook-Drive-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR6436.htm</guid></item><item><title>0 Bedroom Commercial Property, Prestwich £1,200.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Bury-Old-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR6890.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to offer to the market this shop fronted retail unit located on a busy shopping promenade with unallocated parking to the front of the property. Units of this ilk very rarely come to the market so we would expect strong interest so early viewings are highly recommended.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 12:43:18 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Bury-Old-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR6890.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Apartment, Salford £180,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Westfield-Street-Salford-pi-AUBR7468.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this first floor three bedroom apartment located in a quiet development in the heart of Broughton Park, the property offers convenient access to local shops, places of worship and transport links. Properties in the development are unable to be rented.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 01:05:04 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Westfield-Street-Salford-pi-AUBR7468.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Higher Blackley £239,950.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Victoria-Avenue-East-Higher-Blackley-Manchester-pi-AUBR7428.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this semi detached, three bedroom house offering scope of extension (subject to the usual permissions) there are also two reception rooms along with a nicely proportioned garden to rear and off street parking to the front.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:42:31 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Victoria-Avenue-East-Higher-Blackley-Manchester-pi-AUBR7428.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Manchester £1,150.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Hodder-Way-Manchester-pi-AUBR5607.htm</link><description>kargihome are pleased to present this three bedroom semi-detached property which comprises of ; A large living room, conservatory,  large ktichen, with eat in area, paved patio area. The upstairs comprises of; two double bedrooms, single bedroom, separate WC and bathroom</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 03:48:23 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Hodder-Way-Manchester-pi-AUBR5607.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Terrace, Prestwich £195,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Milton-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7585.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to bring to the market this mid terraced two bedroom house offering convenient access to Heaton Park, transport links and Prestwich village is a short distance away. The property is in need of modernisation throughout, offered with no onward chain.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 03:20:47 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Milton-Road-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7585.htm</guid></item><item><title>1 Bedroom Flat, Radcliffe £750.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Blackburn-Street-Radcliffe-Manchester-pi-AUBR7280.htm</link><description>kargihome Homes Ltd are pleased to offer for rent this well presented 1 bedroom apartment located in the centre of Radcliffe.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 03:34:41 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Blackburn-Street-Radcliffe-Manchester-pi-AUBR7280.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Prestwich £275,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Hilton-Lane-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7583.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this elevated semi detached house offering three bedrooms, offering convenient access to local shops and transport links. The property is in need of general modernisation but would make an ideal family home.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 02:35:23 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Hilton-Lane-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7583.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Terrace, Blackburn £595.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Lord-Street-Blackburn-Nelson-pi-AUBR5055.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are pleased to present this two bedroom terraced house in Nelson. The property briefly comprises of; two reception rooms, kitchen, one double bedroom, single bedroom and three piece bathroom.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:11:31 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Lord-Street-Blackburn-Nelson-pi-AUBR5055.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Apartment, Manchester £895.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Sherbourne-Street-Manchester-pi-AUBR6979.htm</link><description>kargihome Estate Agents are pleased to offer this modern, two bed, third floor apartment. With accommodation of: Entrance hall, two good sized bedrooms, living/dining area with through kitchen. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 12:34:07 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Sherbourne-Street-Manchester-pi-AUBR6979.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Terrace, Manchester £1,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Caledonian-Street-Manchester-pi-AUBR7375.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are pleased to present this three bed terraced property with access to a converted loft room!</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 02:17:43 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Caledonian-Street-Manchester-pi-AUBR7375.htm</guid></item><item><title>1 Bedroom Flat, Salford £850.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Nevile-Court-Salford-pi-AUBR5582.htm</link><description>kargihome Homes Ltd are pleased to offer this unfurnished one double bedroom, third floor, purpose built flat located just off Moor Lane. Good sized lounge/kitchen, modern fitted kitchen with appliances, such as oven, mircowave, hob, dishwasher and washing machine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 09:54:27 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Nevile-Court-Salford-pi-AUBR5582.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Flat, Manchester £995.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Mountside-Crescent-Manchester-pi-AUBR4845.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are pleased to offer for rent this unfurnished, ground floor maisonette. Two bedrooms, spacious lounge, modern kitchen with oven, hob &amp; extractor, modern bathroom with shower over, gas central heating, UPVC double glazing, large rear garden,</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 12:47:33 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Mountside-Crescent-Manchester-pi-AUBR4845.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Salford £1,350.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Caldy-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7456.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to bring to the market this renovated, three bedroom, semi detached house. The property was fully renovated in 2024 including new kitchen, bathroom, decor etc. Offering convenient access for local shops, schools and transport links.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 03:12:45 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Caldy-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR7456.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Salford £495,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Singleton-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR6375.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to bring to the market this deceptively spacious semi detached house offering four bedrooms with the main having an en suite and walk in wardrobe, situated in a popular residential location offering easy access to local shops, schools and places of worship.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 03:34:00 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Singleton-Road-Salford-pi-AUBR6375.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Terrace, Radcliffe £950.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Cross-Lane-Radcliffe-Manchester-pi-AUBR6312.htm</link><description>kargihome Homes Ltd are pleased to offer for rent this well presented mid terrace property comprising of :spacious lounge with feature fireplace , dining room,  modern fitted kitchen, access to the rear yard. Good sized bedrooms, family bathroom. UPVC double glazing throughout, gas central heating,</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 09:26:21 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Cross-Lane-Radcliffe-Manchester-pi-AUBR6312.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Detached, Prestwich £1,350.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-East-Meade-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR6241.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to offer to the market this modernised Detached, 3 Bedroom extended home which also has 3 connecting reception areas. The property is offered unfurnished and is available now. Situated in an ideal location for shops and places of worship.</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 10:17:10 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-East-Meade-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR6241.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom End Terrace, Lees £250,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Wild-Street-Lees-Oldham-pi-AUBR7604.htm</link><description>We are delighted to bring to the market this larger than usual stone built end terrace in the popular sought after village of Lees. This unique property provides on street parking with the potential to add off road parking to the rear. There is a low maintenance patio to the front.</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 11:30:47 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Wild-Street-Lees-Oldham-pi-AUBR7604.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Bungalow, Manchester £1,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Kenslow-Avenue-Manchester-pi-AUBR5018.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are pleased to offer, this 2 bed semi-detached bungalow, situated just of Holland Road in the popular area of Crumpsall The property briefly comprises: entrance hall, lounge, kitchen, bathroom/w/c, conservatory, two bedrooms, loft room. There is a garden to the rear.</description><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 11:24:15 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Kenslow-Avenue-Manchester-pi-AUBR5018.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Salford £450,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Norwood-Avenue-Salford-pi-AUBR7597.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are happy to offer to the market this extended semi detached house which boasts four good bedroom (1 en suite) along with two reception rooms and diner kitchen, situated on a quiet cul-de-sac offering convenient access to local shops, schools and places of worship.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 10:32:24 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Norwood-Avenue-Salford-pi-AUBR7597.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Apartment, Salford £900.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Camp-Street-Salford-pi-AUBR3891.htm</link><description>kargihome Estate Agents are proud to offer for rent this fully furnished, modern, two bedroom apartment . The property briefly comprises of: Hallway with a spacious storage cupboard that houses a washer/dryer. Master double bedroom, single bedroom &amp; three piece bathroom.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 05:24:43 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Camp-Street-Salford-pi-AUBR3891.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Detached, Prestwich £375,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Carr-Avenue-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7432.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to bring to the market this extended detached house which offers three bedrooms, two connecting reception rooms and a diner kitchen. The plot still offers scope for further extension (subject to permissions) local shops and schools are a short distance away.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 03:46:10 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Carr-Avenue-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR7432.htm</guid></item><item><title>2 Bedroom Flat, Ashton Under Lyne £850.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Goodhope-Mill-Ashton-Under-Lyne-pi-AUBR7553.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are pleased to offer to the rental market various fully modernised two bedroom apartments within a converted mill, located in the popular Ashton Town Centre.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 11:45:12 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Goodhope-Mill-Ashton-Under-Lyne-pi-AUBR7553.htm</guid></item><item><title>1 Bedroom Flat, Ashton Under Lyne £750.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Goodhope-Mill-Ashton-Under-Lyne-pi-AUBR7550.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are pleased to offer to the rental market various fully modernised one bedroom apartments within a converted mill, located in the popular Ashton Town Centre.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 11:45:40 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Rent-Goodhope-Mill-Ashton-Under-Lyne-pi-AUBR7550.htm</guid></item><item><title>5 Bedroom Detached, Manchester £575,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Bettwood-Drive-Manchester-pi-AUBR7592.htm</link><description>kargihome &amp; Co are delighted to bring to market this extended, detached family home, 5 bedrooms (1 En Suite) set over 3 floors, boasting extensive living space. Situated on a quiet cul-de-sac offering convenient access to schools, places of worship and transport networks including the Metrolink..</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 11:12:39 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Bettwood-Drive-Manchester-pi-AUBR7592.htm</guid></item><item><title>3 Bedroom Terrace, Oldham £140,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Milford-Avenue-Oldham-pi-AUBR7617.htm</link><description>We are pleased to offer this three bed spacious mid terraced house. Situated in a convenient location close to Oldham  and Manchester this mid terrace offers excellent potential to investors . The property is offered with a sitting tenant.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 01:47:33 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Milford-Avenue-Oldham-pi-AUBR7617.htm</guid></item><item><title>4 Bedroom Semi-Detached, Prestwich £350,000.00</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Albert-Avenue-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR5426.htm</link><description>kargihome Estate Agents are pleased to offer for sale, this larger style semi detached property situated on the ever popular Albert Avenue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 05:10:06 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Property-For-Sale-Albert-Avenue-Prestwich-Manchester-pi-AUBR5426.htm</guid></item><item><title>New Revamped Website</title><link>https://www.kargihome/New-Revamped-Website-nw-1000.htm</link><description>We are proud to announce that our newly revamped website has finally gone live. It is a lot more responsive and all of our properties are updated in real time. The new website also gives users the ability to leave us a google review and obtain an instant online valuation. The staff profiles have been updated and every member of staff can contacted directly via the website. We wish you a pleasant surfing experience!</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/New-Revamped-Website-nw-1000.htm</guid></item><item><title>End Of Year Celebrations</title><link>https://www.kargihome/End-Of-Year-Celebrations-nw-1001.htm</link><description>kargihome`s Director and staff, celebrated another successful year at the Taam Grill &amp; Deli  restaurant in Prestwich. A good time was had by everyone and there were smiles all round. 

Unfortunately, our longest standing member of staff; Denise Taylor was unable to attend, due to illness.

There was an emotional element to this year`s party, as it is Ivor Sternberg`s retirement year. Ivor is part of the furniture at kargihome and will be sorely missed by everyone.

We thank you all for your custom throughout the year and here`s to a prosperous 2018!</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/End-Of-Year-Celebrations-nw-1001.htm</guid></item><item><title>Mollie Staines Returns!</title><link>https://www.kargihome/Mollie-Staines-Returns!-nw-1002.htm</link><description>We`re delighted to announce the return of Mollie Staines to our Lettings team. Mollie worked at kargihome back in 2015 and was very popular amongst our Landlords. She took a break to go back to teaching but has realised that her true passion is in property management. Her new role will be Assistant Lettings Manager.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/Mollie-Staines-Returns!-nw-1002.htm</guid></item><item><title>The Legend Has Retired</title><link>https://www.kargihome/The-Legend-Has-Retired-nw-1003.htm</link><description>On Friday 29th June, we had a farewell party at kargihome for Ivor Sternberg, who has been active in the Prestwich property market for close to 30 years. Over 100 people popped in to pay their respects. Ivor has retired just before his 75th birthday. Ivor will be remembered fondly by his many friends and we will miss him here at kargihome. We wish Ivor and his wife Wendy a Happy and Healthy retirement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/The-Legend-Has-Retired-nw-1003.htm</guid></item><item><title>New Valuer</title><link>https://www.kargihome/New-Valuer-nw-1004.htm</link><description>We are delighted to announce the arrival of Leah Garside, who will be a new Valuer in our established team.

Leah has been working locally in property sales for over 10 years. We spot talent when we see it and are delighted that Leah has joined our team! 

Leah brings with her all the local experience, which, combined with her bubbly personality, will make her a big asset at kargihome.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/New-Valuer-nw-1004.htm</guid></item><item><title>LANDLORDS PROMOTION</title><link>https://www.kargihome/LANDLORDS-PROMOTION-nw-1005.htm</link><description>We have today launched our end of year offer, with a HUGE DISCOUNT on our Letting &amp; Management fees. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We are even giving away a FREE gas safety certificate, for all sign-ups by 31st of December 2019. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hurry whilst offer lasts!!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CALL US NOW ON 0161 798 8000</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/LANDLORDS-PROMOTION-nw-1005.htm</guid></item><item><title>STAMP DUTY HOLIDAY!</title><link>https://www.kargihome/STAMP-DUTY-HOLIDAY!-nw-1006.htm</link><description>WELCOME NEWS FOR THE PROPERTY MARKET!! The chancellor has just announced that If you purchase a residential property between 8 July 2020 to 31 March 2021, you only start to pay SDLT on the amount that you pay for the property above £500,000. These rates apply whether you are buying your first home or have owned property before.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is a timely boost for all property buyers, during uncertain times.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/STAMP-DUTY-HOLIDAY!-nw-1006.htm</guid></item><item><title>OUR MOST PRESTIGIOUS PROPERTY EVER!</title><link>https://www.kargihome/OUR-MOST-PRESTIGIOUS-PROPERTY-EVER!-nw-1007.htm</link><description>We are delighted to have won the instruction of the most prestigious property ever marketed by our branch. It is a truly magnificent, 6 bed detached property, situated in the sought after Ringley Park Whitefield.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the words of our Director, Toli Yodaiken; "It is truly an honour for kargihome &amp; Co. to have been appointed as the selling agents for this property and we are hoping that there is a buyer out there who will appreciate this property for it`s breathtaking views, quality fixtures &amp;  fittings and fabulous accommodation".&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For more details, please check the listing on our website, which includes a full 3D virtual tour and drone footage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/OUR-MOST-PRESTIGIOUS-PROPERTY-EVER!-nw-1007.htm</guid></item><item><title>New Staff Appointments &amp; Website Headshots</title><link>https://www.kargihome/New-Staff-Appointments-Website-Headshots-nw-1008.htm</link><description>We are delighted to announce the return of Mollie Staines to kargihome in August. Mollie is now our Lettings Manager and has vast experience in property management. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have also recently appointed Sissi Rose as a Sales &amp; Lettings Executive. Sissi is tasked with conducting our sales progression and also assists with the property management.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We hope that with these appointments, we can continue offering an unparalleled service in all aspects of property sales, lettings and management.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check our website for our new headshots.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;https://www.kargihome/meet-the-team.htm</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.kargihome/New-Staff-Appointments-Website-Headshots-nw-1008.htm</guid></item></channel></rss>